(gentle music)
- And we are back on live.
We are back live. - Yes.
- Yes, for the ship ship Josh of this week.
Love it, let's go.
What's up, Michel, how are you doing?
- I'm doing good.
Back from holiday and it feels like
I didn't go on holiday at all.
- Did you have to manage like 3000 tickets unresolved
because Claude didn't do it properly?
- Yeah, and like 50 branches
where it just pushed everything and then it said,
oh, this one failed, let me create a new branch
and it has like three copies.
- Oh yeah, I got that sometimes too.
Like, yeah, like with Claude, for example,
like I open a chip, you know, like the walkthrough stuff
and I forgot that I clicked on it
and then I asked Claude and say, no, it's not done.
Then he opened the ships.
And so I got some talking on that.
- Yeah, so eventually now I just start with,
hey, check everything that you've built,
test it, merge it and give me a notification
when you're done.
- Yeah, exactly.
I think we need more skills to check what's running
between the 50 terminal open and 25 project running.
- Well, the idea is that I just let it do three or four tasks
I checked it and it continues, but then you go to bed
and you wake up in the morning and it has done like 44 tasks.
- So you still have your agents like running 24/7?
- Yeah, on my Mac mini.
- Oh yeah, nice.
- Yes, but I've added the option that if it is too big
to do at once or it has many points,
just split it into multiple tasks.
- Yeah, which should, yeah.
- And then I said, you have to put an order on it.
And if one to 10 and you can't start on three,
you have to start on one because that was going wrong
in the middle and it said, hey, this is more easier to do.
Let me start with that one.
And then it went, but still that gives issues
when it's thinking by itself.
So you need proper rules.
- Yeah, like the undeterministic aspect
of AI is beating us sometimes.
I never like, you put stuff in cloud.md or agent.md
and still not fucking reading like the global project.
It's annoying.
- Yeah, I think that's like we said
last time, right?
My first round is check if it did read the MD files.
- Yeah, I have a session starts among stuff.
Yeah, I should use it more often because I don't.
But yeah, but then the context getting full
and then you say, okay, compact.
- But then you have my team lead cloud fable
and he always knows the answer.
He always said, oh, he didn't do this.
Let me force it to do it again.
Yeah, let me send it like, no, not the pull request
but the new work tree and then you have 25 work trees
and then you have to do it again, all over again.
But yeah, anyway, what did you build this week, man?
- I think the biggest one was a full
WhatsApp business integration with Meta.
- Oh, cool.
- It was onboarding for WhatsApp business.
So if you have it in your account,
you can either create a new number,
connect your existing number, merge it
between of constantly sync it between your devices.
And yeah, it was a lot more than I thought it would be.
- I had to do that too, like last week
and the Facebook Meta app is pure garbage.
I've created the business organization.
I create the page, I connect the WhatsApp, blah, blah, blah.
I changed the email of my accounts
to have the same organization under the profile.
The business organization lose my ownership
and I don't have it.
So I have a business organization
where I don't have access to it.
I can't even see it.
I can contact support because it's all AI agent
and they don't...
- Yeah, speak to a real human and it says, I am.
- Yeah, and so now I have a business organization
in like completely lost that I need to redo it, like bro.
- Yes.
- And then you try to add an admin
but the admin doesn't have the phone number verified
like a billion dollar company.
And so I'm feeling good about my little pesky bugs now
because if Facebook can't have a proper
ads management platform, yeah, we're good.
- I have always been having issues with everything from Meta.
- Crazy.
- And not even in coding, also just using.
- Yeah, like not working.
- Yeah, and the first thing is finding what you need.
That's the biggest issue.
- Yeah, like everything is everywhere
and you don't need like 90% of the UI and then you open it.
- So I don't know, but I have like a note of deep links
to every page that I need in the beginning
so that I don't have to search the entire menu.
- Yeah, like, so you have a bookmarks, yeah, okay.
- Yeah.
- And basically they have been by coding since 20 years.
- Yeah, but since one of the biggest companies
they did something correct.
- Yeah, but it's not coding.
- No, it is just, oh, we need something else added.
- Exactly, which is basically what we're doing.
- Yeah, but we have good AI, they had like indie devs.
- Anything else, like any multi-billion dollar company
that you have approved it?
- I want it, but it didn't go that hard.
- Wait for February 6th.
- Yeah, well, really looking forward to it,
but I think we just learned today
that you don't put it on high effort
and ask an easy question, right?
- I mean, you tell me, bro,
you are the ones spending tokens
on changing the color of a button and it's still not done.
- I just asked and I thought, if it is that smart
and you put it on X high, doesn't it need to know for,
hey, this is an easy task.
I don't need to do this, this and this.
Just let me change the color.
- Yes, but okay, so I think it's because
when you change like the effort,
it's add thinking between every step
and every tools it's called to reason.
So if you have a simple task, it's better to go down on low
because then it will go straight to the point.
- Yes, well, I found what the issue was
because I wanted to change a button
and there was only one line of code,
just six characters in the CSS file
and eventually it started Chrome.
It looked at it with Chrome.
It made multiple screenshots to determine
what it needs to do.
It measured everything, changed the button
and redid everything, compared it,
wasn't convinced and redid everything
and that just for changing six characters in the CSS file.
- I have the same issue with like the browser,
computer use and the native browser
where codex will open the browser
or take control of my computer to like same thing,
like change the color of something or move a button.
- Yeah. - Or even like
instead of using the CLI, it's using computer use.
So it will connect to my browser,
go to post-hug, for example,
that happened a couple of times.
Go to post-hug, enable the filter flag and stuff.
Everything is accessible via CLI/API.
- Yes.
- And then like, stop using my browser, I'm working.
You are interrupting me.
- Yeah, it's like taking over your PC
when you're doing stuff.
- Yeah, exactly.
And I saw a tweet from Peter from OpenClo
that said, "Yeah, I know it's annoying and I have VMs."
Like he's running like codex into VMs to basically build
because yeah, when you have like the computer use
taking over, that's not the computer anymore.
I'm the captain now.
- Yeah, it just takes over, that's cool.
But are you still using codex?
- So I use, I love Grok.
- Yes.
- Yeah, so right now what I'm doing,
I'm focusing on like QA and one shorting,
like issues which are not on the GitHub board.
So I open a session,
I run the servers and the app in the background.
So like the Grok can monitor the logs.
And I just tell, I take a screenshot and say,
"Yeah, what the fuck is that?
Why this button here?"
Drop it in the terminal or T3 code.
Sometimes I've used T3 code
when I want to use some parallel work trees.
Drop the prompt, drop the image, that, run it.
One or two minutes later, hopefully everything is down.
Then I go back to the page and say, "Yeah, good job, bro."
And then next one.
And also it's batch.
So when you, it's stash, it's yeah, stash, stack, whatever.
The prompt, so I can go to a page, drop the first prompt,
it will execute it.
And then I, but while I do that, I go to the next page,
drop the prompt, same thing, screenshot, blah, blah, blah.
And it will wait for the first one to be executed.
So it doesn't put everything all together and that's dope.
- Yeah, and that was an issue with Opus.
When I put in a second prompt,
before the first one was finished,
it would forget parts of the first one.
- Exactly, but before we had steering with codecs, right?
So you go to the codecs desktop app or whatever,
you drop two prompt and those two prompts
will be steered by each other.
Like the second one, the first one.
But you can also stash them.
And then you have a queue of quick fixes
that will, bluh, bluh, bluh, all done.
- That's cool, yeah, that's lit.
- And so basically what I use,
so Cloud Fable 5 for audits, what I do with like audits,
check the GitHub board, check the issues,
it's like a notch where I check the state of the issues,
compare it against like what we have in the code base.
And if I have something that can be done in parallel,
I will open a work tree directly from Cloud desktop UI,
because I can get the chip, parallel, bluh, bluh, bluh.
And also my cloud is configured to use chat GPT
via the cloud interface.
- Yeah, you have to do that.
- Exactly, I have the subagent on codex.
- Yes, that's cool.
- Yeah, it's lit.
I just need to do that automatically in ship code,
but I love those.
- I think we just switched to grog a week ago, right?
After the previous--
- After Europe allows us to use it.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And I instantly switched to the $300 sub with the discount.
- Me too.
- I can sell one cloud account and take the fucking EV super,
EV let go grog to build stuff.
- Yeah, it just feels like we're going on rocket power.
- Yes, and look like share these tabs,
path grog 4.6 is supposed to come in three days now.
- Ooh, that's nice.
- 4.6, yes.
And grog--
- Yeah, that's three days.
- 4.7, around August 7th,
and 4.8 will be 2.1 a few weeks later.
- 4.7, you mean?
- Yeah, so 4.6 like soon,
and 4.7 at 2.1 trillion parameters will be following soon.
So if they can keep that velocity, that's a banger.
- Well, if they keep this pace up, keep going this fast,
we will have flying computers, coding everything,
just going around you.
This is insane, if you just check where he started
and how far he was behind or how it felt to me
and how far he was behind
and how hard he is going right now, well.
- That's the cursor data.
- Yeah.
- He leapfrog his training models because of that data.
- Well, maybe it was worth the 60 billion, right?
- Yes, 60 billion option that he bought.
But also probably, everyone does that, so anyway.
Probably got a distillation from the other labs,
take all of the models and just like copy paste
and improve, make it better,
and have the compute to process all of those models.
- That's an important one as well.
So if you're not the first one trying to figure everything
out, you just copy paste and improve it.
- And that's why like for the Frontier models labs,
it's better to be second on third
because you can use less capex than the first labs
that are going to drop the next Frontier
because you can distill.
That's what's going on with China right now.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, all of those open source one,
like they wait for February 6th and then,
oh yeah, like 24 hours.
Like the distillation went from three months
to two weeks to 24 hours.
- Yeah.
- So it's, I don't know, it's right,
that was like, Aaron and Sam Aran were right
compared to Daio.
It's all about compute, like compute power.
- Well, he has enough.
- Yeah, I mean, yeah, I mean, dude is going to space, so.
- Yeah, he wants to build a space, so let's go.
I'm just waiting for the moment
that he just connects everything.
So, and he already is doing it, X is connected to Grok,
but if he integrates Starlink and like.
- Yes.
- I don't know whatever he can do.
That will be awesome.
- I hope he's not going to create some content app.
'Cause I don't want to compete with him.
But did you follow the SpaceX stock price?
- Central European time at 22.30.
Tonight he's going to share his first time of figures.
And I think late in the night,
so our time, 22.30,
a lot of people can sell the first shares that they bought.
They were locked up.
So today is a big day for them.
- Okay, okay, that's interesting.
Okay, yeah, so analyst expecting earnings revenue,
7 billion earning per share, loss of coefficient, let's go.
- It's an expectation.
- Yeah.
- They don't know yet until tonight.
- Okay, interesting.
- So I'm really looking forward to what the price is.
- Yeah, I will let it slide again
because like SpaceX is supposed to happen to send people,
like to send people or robots to Mars, right?
That's not happening in the next two weeks.
- No, not in the next two weeks.
- Yeah.
- No.
- So yeah, did you bought SpaceX?
- Not yet.
- I'm waiting for, I'm just really looking forward
to see what it does tonight.
If it goes up like 100%, I'm feeling stupid, but.
- It's not a meme coming, bro.
- It's, no, I was actually thinking
it might even go a bit down
because people can sell the shares.
- Yeah, beta 100, that would be fun.
Yeah, 1.8 on the lowest.
I'm not touching like, not touching.
- Yeah, if you do it, you need to keep it for a long time.
- Yeah.
- It's not a crypto coin where you can sell it in four days.
- I mean, how long did it take to Amazon
to come back from the?
- It took them some time.
- Yeah, like decade.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, see, like, you have some time from SpaceX,
you have 10 years for SpaceX to do exactly that.
But if they can pull that up, that will be the biggest
company in the universe.
- Yeah, but still, if you check Amazon,
it went up from a few dollars, like $1 here.
- Yeah, yeah, a couple of cents.
- $2, so that's a big difference.
SpaceX started really high compared to Amazon.
- Yeah, but also, they're probably like,
I don't know if it's the case for Amazon,
but they can also split the price per stock.
- And you can buy fractional shares now everywhere, right?
- Yeah, yeah, that's no problem.
- So, and you can even like buy stocks of SpaceX on crypto.
- I've seen it, yes, but I'm not touching that one.
- Ever known Jupiter?
- I don't know.
I've been watching like the hack in the hardware wallet.
- Yeah.
- And they made just one line of stupid code
in the entire database or the entire code base.
And people being able to steal money
from a gold wallet that's stored in a vault,
that's a really big issue.
- Yeah, so I just watched a video about that
and the guy explained it.
So basically, the code wallet to generate the seed
used a strong algorithm to generate the seeds,
like 120 bytes algorithm, whatever.
So that's, this one is secure, but they had a fallback
in the generation of the keys.
So for example, if the, like it's a waterfall function
where if the first step is failing for whatever reason,
you still generate the seed with a lower probabilistic.
- To stop it going from infinite amounts of failures.
- Yes, exactly.
So, and then like the hacker, like I was able to data mine
to generate those keys with a good computer.
And the hack is still running right now
because it's able to crack the keys generated.
So, and probably it's thanks to AI, by the way.
- Yeah, of course, AI does a lot.
- Yeah, probably like I use a Fable 5XI on it.
And yeah, that was able to do that
because the project was open source, is open source.
And yeah, so basically it's also an open source
security issues, which later is not open source,
cloud source, yeah.
And hi, Arin and Diaz, thanks for joining us today.
- Okay, cool.
Next, next, next, next, what do we have?
What do we have?
Yeah, I like this one.
Tag, can I ask a question?
Yes, you can.
I mean, you can ask the question,
maybe we will not answer it, but you can always ask.
- Feel free to ask.
- And so, yeah, OpenAI improved the cost,
like the pricing, yeah, the cost of the models
and with 5.6 Sol, they were able to improve
the cost efficiency, capability and speed of 5.6 Luna
by 80%.
- Yeah, that's a lot.
- And some people on the timeline were saying like,
now you can use Luna high, fast,
and have the equivalent of like Sol medium or something,
but for half the price.
- Yeah, that's cool.
Well, it just looks like they put the prices really high
on the hype on the release because everybody is going
to test it, use it and they make a lot of money.
And then afterwards, they have to make sure
that it's correct again and to be able to compete
with the other models.
- Yeah.
- But I was checking my API settings for all the projects
that were still running on like what all the models
and I have like a 4.0 active mini and the normal one.
And I was checking and a 4.1 is even 20% cheaper.
- Damn.
- So you need to keep checking your models
because they update the prices and the other ones,
they keep on the higher prices and the new ones not.
So switching to a better model, getting better results
is even cheaper than just letting it go
how it goes right now.
- That was what we saw when they released the benchmark
and where the price is per task and not per token, right?
Because again, you can be cheaper per token output
but if the result is shit, then you still need to re-prompt
or even use, the task will use more tokens.
So even if it's cheaper, the absolute value in dollars
will be higher anyway.
And okay, so a question I'm taking.
So we're gonna do some orientation now.
Business tech in CSE, what is it?
Do you know?
Is that business tech?
B tech, is that business tech?
- I think so, let me check.
- And will I face problem in finding a good job
in the future when I pass out?
- Yeah. - I mean.
- Bachelor of Science in Computer Science and Engineering.
- Oh yeah, okay.
- Computer Science and Engineering, I'm stupid.
And B tech is business tech?
- Yes, Bachelor of Science.
- Yeah, what would you do?
- Well, honestly, everybody doing computer science
right now, I think eventually AI has already caught up.
So honestly, if you are still doing the education
in the way that they were doing it like five years ago,
then you're behind.
You just need some lessons in how to use AI,
how to understand, and I don't know about you,
but I still see an issue, another issue,
but if my customers and other IT companies
that I work for have the same AIs they can use
and the same capabilities, sometimes even better
because they have a higher budget,
they get worse results because they don't know how to ask
and how to prompt properly.
And they don't understand what the AI is doing in tech.
So you need some basics, but coding yourself,
if you're learning how to do that and how to plan,
yeah, that's a waste of time.
- I mean, yeah, again, it's important to know
what you're asking too, right?
Because Evan, I saw a tweet where instead of prompting
a five sentence to describe a UX/UI effect,
if you know the name of the effect,
then you can just like reduce this prompt in three words
and the output will be better, right?
So same thing for the tech stack.
If you know what the fuck you are doing
and you know what to ask in technical term,
then the model will hallucinate less
or like do more research, et cetera.
So the output will be better, right?
- Yeah.
So experts know, have better output than the random guy
saying, okay, create AGI and make the mistake.
Like that's, I mean, can the models be smart enough
to understand Evan, the stupidest prompt?
Time will tell, but yeah.
I mean, also like, I don't know if you're,
where your base like are renamed, are renamed,
but if you are in the US and you're gonna have to spend
like take a fucking 200 grand loan to spend times
in parties and stuff with friends,
and then in five years you're gonna have,
you will not be able to find a job,
then it's gonna be crazy.
I mean, if you can go to Harvard,
enjoy your time at school.
If you are going to community college
or community university or whatever,
just keep it and build business.
- But if I had to hire people right now,
I would still take the people with some experience
because I know that they can also test the AI
and see if it did something correct.
- Yeah.
- And sometimes you go in the loop
and if you then just don't know what you need to ask
and keep asking the same questions, that's bad.
- Okay, now from India.
Yeah, do you know the educational system in India?
- I know they have some really good universities.
- Yeah, yeah, I mean, yeah.
I think the value of school and university
like definitely still good
if you go to the high ends of them.
But like, yeah, if you're gonna pay
like crazy amount of money for an average school,
better drop out in, I mean, I don't know if I can.
- Don't tell them to drop out.
But if you know what to ask
and then you're already set and ready to go,
but just also make sure that even when you're in school,
just keep using the AI and see what's going on
and what they release in new features
because I think a school is always behind.
- Yeah, no, like during my master's degree,
like I was like coding in Java
and like to learn oriented object programming stuff,
but I never fucking use it like outside of the classroom.
Like it was mental.
And like JavaScript or even PHP, yeah, a bit of PHP,
but everything that I use right now,
I learned by myself, right?
But school give you a framework to sync, learn
and hopefully by yourself, right?
- Yeah, you just have to improve that one.
- Yeah, and as long as you are like,
you know, you like what you're doing
and you will never stop learning
on enjoying like what you do
and you will always find a job
or create your own job anyway.
So like, and business tech and computer science,
like which skill is harder to get?
- Is that a question for me?
I don't know.
The more an AI can do, the easier it is.
- Yeah, yeah.
But can you build expertise in business faster
than development?
Would you say it's easier for a dev to catch up in business
or a business sales guys to catch up in tech?
- Yeah, the other way around.
Business sales guys catching up in tech.
- Yeah.
- Because honestly, the business sales guys,
they do so many talks.
They hear so many stuff from people doing difficult talks
and they should just get like,
I was having it here, like something like this,
like the pocket where you can just, you click it
and then record your entire sales conversation,
makes a summary, makes points to go.
If you just record them all and put them into an AI,
have them analyze and explain it to you
at the end of the day.
- Yeah.
- And you're doing like three or four sales calls per day,
that will just put you on to speed
and you will learn so much.
- I mean, if you just like do by,
if you learn by doing something
instead of like spending eight hours per day in a classroom.
- Yeah.
- So, Irene, did we answer your question?
Are you gonna drop out after this live?
Let's go.
What to do to make me more valuable?
Like what skill to develop?
Just be able to learn everywhere, like don't be lazy.
Yeah, don't be lazy.
It's actually a good one.
- Yeah, do what you like.
And even if it is a niche
and there are only a few people doing it, that's no problem.
Just make sure that you're good at it and go.
- Yeah.
Try to be in the top 1% in the world at what you do.
And even if you don't do it,
you will be better than fucking like everyone
who dropped out before you reached the point
where you are right now.
- I think the only thing is that people keep telling
and isn't true is that with AI everything can be done
in a few minutes.
I'm still spending a lot of time using AI coding
and doing everything.
- Yeah, I mean, the critical thinking
and thinking will not go away like anytime soon.
All of the AI labs are preaching that yeah,
coding will be solved in six months
and it was like two years ago.
- Yes.
And then still it makes stupid mistakes.
And if you have two different AIs communicating
about the problem, eventually after five, six rounds,
they can still say, "I don't agree with the other one."
And it just, that's it.
- Oh, exactly.
Last one, will electrical and communication engineering
be superior than CSE in the future?
- Yeah, really hard to tell
because you don't know when it's going.
- We don't know what's gonna happen
in the next six months, right?
Like, so, I mean, it's right now, it's bit like,
we're going so fast and so far from the last two years,
for example, that predicting what AI gonna be able
to produce in the next six, 12 to 18 months, like mental.
Yeah, it'd be like, "Hey bro, like try to apply
with Elon Musk, he needs some smart people
for SpaceX, Tesla and et cetera."
So let's go, just be the world-class guy
in whatever the fuck you want to do.
And do you need school for that?
- No, you need to be able to just learn a lot,
keep asking questions and think for yourself.
- Yeah, did, Arin, Arin, like, did you ask Claude what?
Like those questions, that would be curious.
- Okay, so another topic, open source again.
Gwen's 3.8 has been released like yesterday.
Yes.
- I didn't see it yet.
- Like, bro.
Oh, okay.
Pro benchmark, so, okay, what is it?
Oh, that's probably Fable.
It's basically much like those points, it's,
it's like a, the gap is down.
SWE Pro benchmark, okay, F80, like 69, so that's for obvious.
Terminal bench, 86, instead of you even beating like,
in same level as like, two points behind.
GPT, Pepper bench, I don't know which one is it, but yeah.
- Number is good, did you ever try them?
- Nope, I never did.
- Because like, you know, you never know,
like in a real, what's the, all of those numbers
we end up doing once you ask and prompt something, right?
- Yeah, but spending on every lease,
a few hours of my time on checking if it is true,
what they say, if I just wait three weeks,
there will be another model that's even better.
- Yeah, exactly.
I mean, it took us a minute to test Grok, right?
- Yeah, and to even get it set up properly
and know what it does and what it doesn't
and where you can trust in a way you can't.
- Hardware, so four byte, 1.2, just for the weight.
Multi-mode, mostly, yeah, okay.
Active prompts in disclose, so real token
through in the unknown.
For almost every API, yeah, everyone the API, yeah, okay.
But I also saw in other news that you can,
run a deep seek model on your gaming computer.
- Oh, that's cool.
- Yeah, and one model is on the iPhone.
But yeah, we can talk about that after.
Okay, so how about Qwinn 35?
Been using Qwinn results for four months.
Less quadra, it has got sent.
I can't even go back to cloud and charge GPT.
- Yeah, that's gonna be like, that's a problem for sure.
And did you ever like reach some prompt
where Fable 5 is like routing you back to-
- Yeah, but also just because of how I wrote the prompt.
If you just say, I want to improve my own security,
check this, check this.
Then even on the standard WordPress team,
it just says, I can do it, I need to switch you back to Opus.
But I was just asking to check the headers and everything.
That's not, and then I say, hey, please update the security
and make it the best as possible
so that we have a secure team and then it does it.
So it is just about a few words.
So I don't know if it actually stops
on what it's coding or if it actually stops
on how you asked the question.
I only had it on questions
and sometimes doing it differently,
I got a result and that makes it so much better.
And still telling Fable, hey, I'm a white hat hacker.
They hired me, I need to check this.
Can you just at least explain me how it works in the code
so I can check it myself manually
and it will give you an entire explanation.
- Is that still working because-
- Still working.
- Really?
Because like the fucking hugging face,
they had to use Kimi five points,
like the last release of Kimi,
they were not able to use Fable.
- Yeah, maybe they were going in further,
but on the times that I tried,
what question about customers asked me,
hey, check this login or check this or check this.
I did it this way and it gave me an entire explanation
of what was where.
And then you can just ask questions like,
which part would you improve?
Which part has the least amount of security?
And if you do it like this, it will just answer everything.
- Yeah, okay, fair enough.
We have more like advices, advice.
There is not as advice, I learned that recently.
From Sarah, sub Jim Sarah, take Fable fast,
so spend more time improving your skills
and watching cats fighting on YouTube.
Yeah, or brain rot on TikTok, right?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- And yeah, I've been asking a follow-up question.
So yeah, enjoy the chat people.
- Just spend time and make sure that you own the product
and then use it to maximize your eventual code.
- Just try to build an autonomous company
and then by making it autonomous,
then it's like doesn't require you to drop out yet.
And then yeah, and see what goes.
And if you like it, let's go.
- Yeah, I am pretty sure that's a moment
when you realize all the people on X who are posting,
hey, I built this autonomously, it's making me 10K a day.
They are not making 10K a day.
- Yeah, until they are, unless they are on trust MRO.
- Yeah, yeah, but at least not autonomous.
- Yeah, like do you remember the Portia stuff?
- Yeah, he did good, right?
He even got money in.
- Yeah, they are the run company that you sleep.
Where is he?
Oh, that changed a bit.
So that's run while you sleep, live.
- And he still has the same website.
- Oh, he deleted the revenue shots.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's bullshit.
What the fuck is going on?
Because yeah, he raised like multiple millions
from Silicon Valley investors, so.
- Yeah, and he's just still a one man company.
- Yeah.
Yeah, bro, like two views.
Even us, we make like more impression.
- Yeah, well, I make the most impressions
when I do a reply on Elon.
- Yeah, no shit.
Yeah, 30 million at 250 valuation, like bro, like what?
- Yeah.
- That's, it was 20 to, no, 250 million, yeah.
Like what?
- Well, sometimes you don't get it,
but possibly they saw something that we didn't.
- Yeah, the progress is something like really, yeah.
That is something we don't see for sure.
- Yeah, well, there's a nice guy
and they want to go to parties at the same time.
- That's not, it's not a no name.
Like he has some background for sure.
- Yeah.
- We can check him like quickly.
I built four products before Portia or Fair,
then I built one that felt too crazy, too ambitious, okay.
For second, I'm on Mount Fuji, okay.
Serving was this modern scale, it's no joke.
I play market.
One person I have reached 10K paying customers,
generally 10 million in revenue this year.
What?
Okay, whatever.
Back to orientation.
Randomly popped in my feed and you guys really helped me.
Thanks, appreciate you.
- Oh, cool.
- Thanks, thanks to the Argo.
And yeah, if you, so subscribe then like the video
and talk with your friend, like share it with your friend.
Thank you.
And yeah, you're welcome.
And come back in the chat if you need like, yeah.
I don't know if you want to drop out now,
but just keep grinding, man.
I don't know if you want me to go.
Cool, next.
So Quen, Grok, 4.8, we did that path.
Yeah, do we have anything like to mention?
- Yeah, Grok is getting 4.6 in three days.
- No, I know.
I showed you.
(laughing)
Oh yeah.
I mean, OpenAI, have you seen like the blog post
from OpenAI saying Apple like--
- Yeah, so this morning I didn't read it, so.
- Okay.
- I see a lot of people replying.
- I have that too, okay.
Yeah, shit, that's gonna make a shit ton of you, man.
X, so deck, deck, deck,
OpenAI path, okay, deck, deck, deck, where is it?
I read it like, the fuck?
Where is it?
Is it slow?
Okay, yes, okay, okay.
I lost it.
Yes.
So Apple is getting this wrong.
So basically, to summarize quickly, Apple accused OpenAI
of industrial spying.
Like, one of the guys they hired from Apple stole data
and tried to give it to OpenAI.
So it's like industrial espionage.
- Yeah, that was a few weeks ago, right?
- Yes, and look, hello.
Name, okay, because they're fucked up too.
Lawyer, or like the biggest sentence.
They now admit that the outside lawyers emailed
the wrong person after confusing two Asian men.
- Oh, that's bad.
So they gave the information to the wrong person.
- Yeah, and like the whole blog post is about OpenAI
saying that basically, nobody wants the data
that you think we stole from you.
And imagine the cost of lawyers between Apple
and OpenAI and those talkers.
- That's going hard.
- They can't even email the wrong, the correct person.
- Yeah.
- So yeah, like, I don't know if you want to read it now,
but like they drop everything.
- It's just in public.
- Like yeah, laws in public, man.
Yeah, law suit in public.
- That's cool.
- But how do you come back from that?
Like fucking clown, man.
- Well, normally I would say
that's why you're hiring lawyers, right?
- Yeah, right, yeah.
- I guess not.
- Increase your subscription to chat GPT and like check it.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that would be fun to do the experiment
to see if the AI could detect the fact
that they send an email to the wrong person.
- Well, it should be able to.
- Yeah, I mean, if it's a spinning mistake at some point,
the model should be able to detect it.
- Yeah, see, okay.
So I accused Tang Tan of trying to get
and use the trade secret.
Tang has always been clear with the team
that we do not want it
and must not use any confidential information
from other company.
Tang served Apple for more than 24 years
and was widely known
as one of the most innovative leader in the company.
Why this guy would do that half?
Like nuts.
- No, probably he's just proud of what he builds with Apple.
- Yeah, no, exactly.
- So he's not going to ruin it.
- And he knows that the reputation will fumble
and it will be mega fucked if it does that.
So like, I can't believe,
because again, you can't really hire someone
that stole information from another company
because maybe there is a chance
that he will do that to you too, right?
- Yeah.
And that's it, if it comes out, you can't use it.
You have to pay the other company
or you go bankrupt or whatever.
So if you're a big company, you don't want to do it.
- Yeah, it's crazy.
Yeah, it's like too risky, right?
I mean, there was a case like a few years ago
when two competitors send spies between each other.
They were like an employee from a company, A,
send the guys to get hired to the other company
and they were like spying.
And they caught them up with like some email
invisible character or something.
- Like a white character on a white background.
- Yeah, exactly.
And so they can trace the origin of the leakers that way.
Like some only put like that.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, that's crazy.
Okay, agent, oh yeah, okay.
So there is also some story
about Fable 5 deleting a server, that's fun.
- Yeah, well, you still know AI can make mistakes, right?
And if you use AI on a live production server,
you give it FTP or SSH,
you really need to make proper backup before you do it.
- Sorry, the dog, did you hear the dog?
- Yeah.
- Okay, I'm gonna open the door.
- Okay.
And back.
- And we are so back.
Yeah, so don't let run your agent on production, I guess.
- Well, you can do it for checking and testing,
but make sure that you have a backup
and that you don't give it access to everything.
- That's what the guy said.
I have a offsite backup, so data is data,
so total loss was minimal.
And that's a lesson.
Makes backup for the sensitive data
before giving access to your code base.
- I know some people just with small websites
and not a big code base,
but just small things, WordPress team,
they just log in and they do everything live,
but that's like team changes and that's no problem at all.
- Yeah, I know, I mean like-
- 2.2 million files, that's a lot.
- That's a big code base for sure.
- Yeah.
- But yeah, I mean, like we're not here yet.
Like I don't think AI can take the control
of a hospital just yet, but yeah.
- But even if AI does it properly,
he just needs to check the live server,
have access to a different server or ask it,
create a development or a staging or whatever,
change it there, have you approve and then publish it live.
That's how it should do.
- Okay, so yeah, you have like deterministic gradual.
I have some scripts that track the files,
like for some critical files
or like not delete those file stuff.
And that works pretty great on the CI/CD, so.
I think we're good, man.
- Yeah, we have those things.
- Yeah, so that should be enough shows,
enough shorts from between last week and this week.
So yeah, I think that we can wrap it up here.
Oh, no, wait.
- What did we miss?
- I'm gonna show you
because I wanted to talk to you about that too.
Thank you.
GPT 5.6 context can cross the 272K window,
and then you go into the higher usage.
I think it's more expensive after this window.
So compact your session.
- Yes, don't give them money for free.
- Exactly, and save your token.
- Yes.
- My great idea giving is context window.
But yeah, like that was a bug.
I mean, the pull request is still open.
That's why also open source is nice
because, okay, so when you are in crypto project
and it's open source, hackers can hack,
but people can open an issue/pull request
to fix the issues.
- And you have a lot of tech guys
who just love going through code and finding issues.
- Yeah, or send more agents who use more subscription
than your own little 200 or so.
But sometimes they just do it in the free time for fun.
- Yeah, I mean, did you ever?
- I'm always too busy.
I don't have free time.
- Let's make money first.
- Yeah.
- And that's a good conclusion for the life.
- Exactly, build, build, build, make money,
and then enjoy the life.
- Exactly, so everyone, thank you so much.
Thank you, Sara, and thank you, Arinand, for joining us
and commenting, participating.
That's a pleasure to have you here.
And Michal, thank you so much for your time.
- Thank you too.
- We will see you next week, same time, same place,
and maybe you're gonna see us with some shorts.
- On the timeline.
- Yes.